[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Captain Ahab, who is captain of the Pequod, has a 1st mate named Ishmael.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the first Saw movie, the character named Mark, committed workmans comp fraud.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country is known as \u00d6sterreich in their native language?", "correct_answer": "Austria", "incorrect_answers": ["Bulgaria", "Germany", "The Netherlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What fruits are added between the layers as well as on top of the Black Forest cake?", "correct_answer": "Cherries", "incorrect_answers": ["Bananas", "Figs", "Peaches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The outbreak of what deadly disease is often referred to as Black Death?", "correct_answer": "Plague", "incorrect_answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Malaria", "Cholera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the hit comedy Napoleon Dynamite, Napoleon is a member of the Happy Hands Club, a sign language troupe. What was the name of the song they performed in class?", "correct_answer": "The Rose", "incorrect_answers": ["Paradise City", "Old McDonald Had a Farm", "Id Like to Teach the World to Sing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cats twitch the tips of their tails slightly when hunting or when angry, while stronger twitching indicates what?", "correct_answer": "Displeasure", "incorrect_answers": ["Stress", "Boredom", "Playfulness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In terms of population of the city proper, which is the first capital city with over 10,000,000 people?", "correct_answer": "Moscow", "incorrect_answers": ["Karachi", "Sao Paulo", "New York City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This large cat breed, created in the United States, has rabbit-like fur of medium length, rectangular body, and a fatty pad in the lower abdomen.", "correct_answer": "Ragamuffin", "incorrect_answers": ["Balinese", "California Spangled Cat", "Munchkin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many films did Mel Brooks write and direct from 1968 to 1995?", "correct_answer": "11", "incorrect_answers": ["7", "15", "19"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of Lucie and her father in the movie A Tale of Two Cities?", "correct_answer": "Manette", "incorrect_answers": ["Jarvis", "DeFarge", "Alexander"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gabriel Byrne appeared in the 1981 film Excalibur, directed by John Boorman.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]